<item>
	<title>[COLOR red]Contact @Shepo06 for requests or report any broken links[/COLOR]</title>
	<link></link>
	<thumbnail>http://i.imgur.com/CyTtpgR.png</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://i.imgur.com/AsYemPq.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR red]---------------------------------------------------------------[/COLOR]</title>
	<link></link>
	<thumbnail>http://i.imgur.com/CyTtpgR.png</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://i.imgur.com/AsYemPq.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Saul 'Canelo' Alvarez vs Erislandy Lara[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Saul 'Canelo' Alvarez vs Erislandy Lara</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<summary>The Canelo Alvarez-Erislandy Lara fight featured the combination of two legendary Latino boxing traditions. Alvarez, the 23-year-old matinee idol from Guadalajara, represented the Mexican school of boxing – the art of controlled aggression. Lara, the amateur world champion from Guantanamo, represented the Cuban school of boxing – mastery of the ring and technical precision. Lara entered the fight as the WBA Super Welterweight Champion, but the title was not on the line. The contracted weight limit for the fight was 155 pounds, one pound over the super welterweight limit. The fight was televised live on pay-per-view. It generated more than $17 million from around 325,000 buys.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>http://uptobox.com/0knhwn8m2uhy</link>
	<thumbnail>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/35409258/canelo-vs-lara-poster.0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://static.boxrec.com/thumb/b/b3/Canelo-alvarez-vs-erislandy-lara-10-photo-by-naoki-fukuda.jpg/450px-Canelo-alvarez-vs-erislandy-lara-10-photo-by-naoki-fukuda.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Tony Bellew vs Nathan Cleverly (WBO Light Heavyweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Tony Bellew vs Nathan Cleverly (WBO Light Heavyweight Title)</title>
		<year>2011</year>
		<summary>t was announced that Bellew would fight Nathan Cleverly in Liverpool, on 15 October 2011, for the WBO light heavyweight title. The attritional nature of the fight made it difficult to score and in Liverpool, an ill-tempered build-up to the fight culminated in a flare-up at Friday's weigh-in and Cleverly was given a hostile reception by a partisan crowd at the Echo Arena.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>https://youtu.be/xPS2qeFpVPg?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</link>
	<thumbnail>http://static.boxrec.com/thumb/e/ec/Nathan_Cleverly_vs._Tony_Bellew_%28poster%29.jpg/300px-Nathan_Cleverly_vs._Tony_Bellew_%28poster%29.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://cf.c.ooyala.com/hubXZ0cTph4k9RuRyt5JIxHYO9_5fVSF/x0JBUkvnwpAy-qi34xMDoxOjBzMTt2bJ</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Tony Bellew vs Ilunga Makabu (WBC Cruiserweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Tony Bellew vs Ilunga Makabu (WBC Cruiserweight Title)</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<summary>After achieving everything domestically and on the European stage, Tony Bellew looked to finally win the elusive world title that evaded him at light heavyweight, despite two attempts. A move up to cruiserweight in in 2014 and six fights later, Bellew is presented with another opportunity at a world title shot as he faced Ilunga Makabu for the vacant WBC world cruiserweight belt. However Ilunga Makabu was possibly the most dangerous cruiserweight out there, while he did have some flaws and could be outboxed to a certain point this man hit so hard it usually doesn’t matter. Makabu’s southpaw stance was tricky and his left hook would give you nightmares for days after it had put you to sleep.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/6II_qh94__4?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/UrK_qGgtY6I?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video-113129151_456239298</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://atbf1.allthebestfights.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/smith-vs-reynoso-poster-2016-05-29.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://e1.365dm.com/16/05/16-9/20/tony-bellew-ilunga-makabu-boxing_3472030.jpg?20160524084802</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Nigel Benn vs Gerald McClellan[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Nigel Benn vs Gerald McClellan</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<summary>Nigel Benn vs Gerald McClellan was a professional boxing match contested on 25 February 1995 for the WBC super middleweight championship. Benn was victorious when McClellan was counted out in the 10th round while dropped on one knee. Shortly after the match ended, McClellan collapsed and fell into a coma for two weeks. As a result of the injuries endured during the fight, McClellan is blind, hearing-impaired, suffers short-term memory loss, and needs to use a wheelchair. It has been described as "a fight that will be embedded forever in the memories" of those that watched it.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video-154239_167338812</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/j9s1_k2LNUk?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://africanring.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/NIGEL-BENN-VS-GERALD-McCLELLAN.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://sports-images.vice.com/images/articles/meta/2016/02/25/untitled-article-1456402724.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Adrien Broner vs Marcos Maidana[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Adrien Broner vs Marcos Maidana</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<summary>In 2013, the fight between Adrien Broner and Marcos Maidana took place at the Alamodome in San Antonio. The flash Adrien Broner, a skillful boxer and provocateur from Cincinnati was at twenty-four, regarded as probably the best in the world at lightweight. His opponent was Marcos Maidana, from Argentina, who held versions of the world title at super-lightweight and welterweight and was involved in a number of exciting fights during his career.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>https://youtu.be/y7_03tcbhbc?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.boxinghd.com/images/1421067_10151675018350756_520331439_o1.png</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://www.ringtv.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/file_182633_8_broner_vs_maidana_1_20131214_2023813865.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Joe Calzaghe vs Jeff Lacy (WBO, IBF & The Ring Super Middleweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Joe Calzaghe vs Jeff Lacy</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<summary>Joe Calzaghe had been WBO super middleweight champion for over eight years having beaten Chris Eubank for the vacant title in 1997. He had held onto his belt for 17 defences and was considered on the fringes of being one of the best fighters of the world. Jeff Lacy was an American champion who had been compared to Mike Tyson in size and was considered one of the hottest prospects in American boxing.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/ilmQaPdFp1g?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video-25244523_171616769</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/8fB3FN7ckfg?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/3VSjzPJ-p-U?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/302/0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/pBbEDZfoJjA/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<plugin>
	<title>[COLOR white]Julio César Chávez[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Julio César Chávez</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<summary>Undefeated at 43-0, he stopped Mario Martinez (KO 8) in 1984 for the WBC super featherweight title. Nine successful defenses followed before beating Edwin Rosario (TKO 11) for the WBA lightweight title in 1987. He added the WBC version with a win over Jose Luis Ramirez (TW 11) in 1988. Chavez became a three-division world champion when he won the WBC junior welterweight crown from Roger Mayweather (TKO 10) in 1989. His impressive string of 12 title defenses included wins over Hector Camacho and Greg Haugen in front of a record crowd of 132,274 fans and, in 1990, he stopped IBF king Meldrick Taylor with 2 seconds left in the fight to unify titles. Chavez moved up in weight and drew with WBC welterweight champion Pernell Whitaker in a 1993 title go. After compiling an 89-0-1 record, he lost the WBC junior welter title to Frankie Randall in 1994 (L 12). He reclaimed the title in the rematch (TW 8) and reigned until losing to Oscar De La Hoya in 1996 (TKO by 4). Chavez challenged for world titles three more times (D 12 Miguel Angel Gonzalez, TKO by 8 De La Hoya and TKO by 6 Kostya Tszyu) before retiring in 2005 with a professional record of 107-6-2 (88 KOs). During his career, he registered wins over Ruben Castillo, Sammy Fuentes, Rocky Lockridge, Juan LaPorte, Tony Lopez and Joey Gamache. Possessor of a great chin, Chavez used a relentless, aggressive style and vicious body attack to become a national hero in Mexico and one of the most popular fighters in history.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PL42eJuahPR3JbBbF0kh_hX_actq_cG542/</link>
	<thumbnail>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CZMyyu0WAAIlQeE.jpg:large</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/3/30/Julio_Cesar_Chavez1_Champ.jpg</fanart>
</plugin>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Oscar De La Hoya vs Floyd Mayweather Jr (WBC Light Middleweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Oscar De La Hoya vs Floyd Mayweather Jr</title>
		<year>2007</year>
		<summary>De La Hoya vs. Mayweather: The World Awaits was a super welterweight superfight which took place on May 5, 2007, at the MGM Grand Arena in Las Vegas, Nevada between six-division world champion Oscar De La Hoya (38-4, 30 KO) and undefeated four-division champion Floyd Mayweather Jr. (37-0, 24 KO). At the time, the bout was the most lucrative boxing match ever, with over $130 million in generated revenue.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>https://youtu.be/1KhBzF6UX_0?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</link>
	<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/b/bf/De_La_Hoya_vs_Mayweather_poster.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aVXSLuuvR3I/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Oscar De La Hoya vs Félix Trinidad (IBF & WBC Welterweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Oscar De La Hoya vs Félix Trinidad</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<summary>Oscar De La Hoya vs Félix Trinidad, billed as The Fight of the Millennium, was held in Las Vegas, Nevada, on September 18, 1999, to unify the WBC and IBF's world Welterweight championships. Planned by promoters Bob Arum and Don King, it pitted WBC world champion Oscar de la Hoya, a Mexican-American, versus Puerto Rican IBF world champion Félix Trinidad. It was the last of the so-called superfights of the 20th century.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/UESUw5WDtP0?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/a7UtsMPsSCE?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/86/0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/72/2.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Michael Dokes vs. Mike Weaver II (WBA Heavyweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Michael Dokes vs. Mike Weaver II (WBA Heavyweight Title)</title>
		<year>1983</year>
		<summary>It was like the difference between December and May. When Michael Dokes lifted Mike Weaver's WBA heavyweight title five months ago at Caesars Palace in Las Vegas, the consensus was that Referee Joey Curtis had prematurely stopped the fight after only 63 seconds. True, Weaver had been knocked down, but otherwise he seemed O.K. That night Dokes bathed in champagne, but not praise</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/mdxeuswM73w?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/YiAdOhb9rUQ?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.bestboxingblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/08/Dokes-vs.-Weaver.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://static.boxrec.com/thumb/3/3f/Dokes-v-Weaver-II-562a.jpg/325px-Dokes-v-Weaver-II-562a.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Carl Frampton vs Scott Quigg (IBF & WBA World Super-Bantamweights Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Carl Frampton vs Scott Quigg (IBF & WBA World Super-Bantamweights Titles)</title>
		<year>2016</year>
		<summary>Five years in the making, unbeaten super-bantamweights Frampton and Quigg finally collided. The two had expressed respect for each other in the past but as fight night neared, tempers where fraying. There was the fractious face-off at the Manchester leg of the media tour, then the changing room row and the brief tussle at the final press conference and finally trainers Shane McGuigan and Joe Gallagher clashed at the weigh-in. Those events would soon be rendered pretty irrelevant, though, when the opening bell cut the engine of the hype machine and the pair got down to business. The bookies had Frampton a slight favourite, but the phrase 'genuine 50-50' has seldom been used as much as in the build-up to a fight...</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>http://streamcloud.eu/usgu5anaspns/boxing.2016.02.27.carl.frampton.vs.scott.quigg.ppv.internal.pdtv.x264.c4tv.mp4.html</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video20548138_171585928</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://ticketnews.eventim.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/Frampton-Quigg-Poster.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/vKVkGw8Sx6Q/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Carl Froch vs George Groves I (IBF & WBA Super-Middleweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Carl Froch vs George Groves I (IBF & WBA Super-Middleweight Titles)</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<summary>Carl Froch vs. George Groves, billed as the Battle of Britain, was a professional boxing match contested between Carl Froch and George Groves. The event took place on 23 November 2013 at the Manchester Arena in Manchester, England, with Froch's unified WBA (Regular) and IBF super-middleweight titles on the line.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/1xvFXxe-c14?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/cSQZyFO2Sz4?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/3/3d/Froch-GrovesI.jpg/250px-Froch-GrovesI.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://i.huffpost.com/gen/1479631/images/o-CARL-FROCH-GEORGE-GROVES-facebook.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Carl Froch vs George Groves II (IBF & WBF Super-Middleweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Carl Froch vs George Groves II (IBF & WBF Super-Middleweight Titles)</title>
		<year>2014</year>
		<summary>Carl Froch and George Groves first fought on 23 November 2013 at the Manchester Arena. In that fight, Froch's two world titles were also at stake. Groves scored a surprise knockdown in the opening round and went on to build up a lead on all three judges' scorecards. In round nine, the fight ended in highly controversial circumstances when Froch managed land a series of punches to hurt Groves, which prompted referee Howard Foster to stop the fight on a technical knockout. The result was heavily protested by Groves and his team, as well as by fans and the media, creating immediate demand for a rematch.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>https://vk.com/video5663288_169868729</link>
	<thumbnail>https://mmaoddsbreaker.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/Froch-Groves-Poster.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://video.skysports.com/I5dTZmYjE6mU-Eibvx5OfZVz2fZf36P8/promo320601496</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Carl Froch vs Mikkel Kessler I (WBC Super Middleweight Title @ Super Six World Boxing Tournament)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Carl Froch vs Mikkel Kessler I</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<summary>The first fight between Mikkel Kessler and Carl Froch can be considered a classic, it was a great performance by both boxers, some tough exchanges and an exciting ending! The undefeated Carl Froch entered the fight with a record of 26-0-0 (20 knockouts) while Mikkel Kessler had a record of 42-2-0 (32 knockouts). Kessler vs Froch was valid for the WBC super middleweight title (Froch’s third defense) but it was also scheduled for the Super Six World Boxing Classic: super middleweight boxing tournament won by Andre Ward.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>http://www.dailymotion.com/video/xpo24n_carl-froch-vs-mikkel-kessler-2010-04-24_sport</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video136166840_167286604</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/b4/90/8a/b4908a7de070935440a2b01257bfa08e.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://www.theboxingobserver.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/Carl-Froch-Mikkel-Kessler-3.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Carl Froch vs Mikkel Kessler II (IBF & WBA Super Middleweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Carl Froch vs Mikkel Kessler II</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<summary>The second meeting was a close fight with some spectacular exchanges in the last part of the bout. Carl Froch (30-2-0, 22 KOs) entered as the No.2 super middleweight in the world while Mikkel Kessler (46-2-0, 35 KOs) entered as the No.4. In their first fight Kessler defeated Froch by unanimous decision (October 24, 2010); this second fight is valid for the IBF and WBA Super World super middleweight titles. </summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/hkceZf16s04?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>http://vidto.me/iicy9x4ki4cs.html</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://static.boxrec.com/thumb/8/84/Carl_Froch_vs._Mikkel_Kessler_2_%28poster%29.JPG/250px-Carl_Froch_vs._Mikkel_Kessler_2_%28poster%29.JPG</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://cdn.vox-cdn.com/thumbor/E6RhhVurGuOKfSdeO6t8ELqsL_M=/0x90:4000x2757/1200x800/filters:focal(0x90:4000x2757)/cdn.vox-cdn.com/uploads/chorus_image/image/13656091/169483344.0.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]George Groves vs Martin Murray (WBA Interntional Super Middleweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>George Groves vs Martin Murray (WBA Interntional Super Middleweight Title)</title>
		<year>2016</year>
		<summary>Groves & Murray Between them, shared seven world title attempts in two weight divisions, yet both had been denied the ultimate prize. Both where seasoned, strong-willed competitors, yet both had shown either limitations or degrees of vulnerability. It was an especially significant night for Groves - an A-list fighter having made significant sums from his contests with Carl Froch, and was soon to become a father. He acknowledged as much, drawing on the tutelage of rising trainer Shane McGuigan and his father, the former world champion Barry McGuigan. Murray had certainly pushed Groves's buttons in the build-up, claiming that the Londoner had only made his name on the back of two fights - both defeats - against Froch. It was like a red rag to the flame-haired fighter. Groves was not shy of landing a few verbal upper-cuts himself, especially when recalling Murray's defeat to Gennady Golovkin, the middleweight world No 1 and one of the most feared punchers on the planet.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>https://youtu.be/kPQXgJ1rFRM?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.georgegroves.com/itemimages/grovesvmurrayposter1.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://e0.365dm.com/16/04/16-9/20/groves-murray-graphic-cover-box-office_3455308.jpg?20160425214121</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Ricky Hatton vs Kostya Tszyu (IBF & WBU Welterweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Ricky Hatton vs Kostya Tszyu (IBF & WBU Welterweight Titles)</title>
		<year>2005</year>
		<summary>Ricky Hatton vs. Kostya Tszyu was a boxing Light Welterweight fight on June 4, 2005 between Ricky Hatton and Kostya Tszyu at the Manchester Evening News Arena in Manchester, England. 22,000 crammed into the arena to watch one of the biggest upsets in British Boxing History.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/VIdXRTRO6oA?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video7187965_164198300</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/149/0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://video.skysports.com/JobnVnYTE6N50AAnNV4t85nmX4fKg8VA/promo314553088</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]David Haye v Tony Bellew[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>David Haye v Tony Bellew</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<summary>Bellew sparked a war of words when he called for a domestic clash with Haye in his post-fight interview after knocking out Ilunga Makabu to claim the WBC cruiserweight title at Goodison Park. Both men had shared a fiery sparring session in the past, but Haye mocked this verbal challenge until the Merseysider climbed out of the ring to confront him following his stoppage win over BJ Flores. Haye agreed to face Bellew at heavyweight and they had set the scene for the showdown by trading blows and insults at bad-tempered press conferences.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video250406938_456239132</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video369568958_456239018</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video-75385532_456241634</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://d1ya1fm0bicxg1.cloudfront.net/2016/11/david-haye-vs-tony-bellew-tickets_03-04-17_3_58382eba81735.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://e2.365dm.com/16/06/16-9/20/david-haye-boxing-tony-bellew_3476711.jpg?20160601105541</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Evander Holyfield vs Riddick Bowe I (IBF, WBA, WBC and Lineal Heavyweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Evander Holyfield vs Riddick Bowe I (IBF, WBA, WBC and Lineal Heavyweight Titles)</title>
		<year>1992</year>
		<summary>Evander Holyfield vs. Riddick Bowe was a professional boxing match that took place on November 13, 1992 in Las Vegas, Nevada. The fight was contested for the undisputed world heavyweight championship, which consisted of the WBA, WBC, IBF and Lineal championships.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/WPejZhE6cq0?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/nqOlBCSu4Z8?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/416/0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://www.ringnews24.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/Evander-Holyfield-vs-Riddick-Bowe.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Bernard Hopkins vs Oscar De La Hoya (IBF, Lineal, The Ring, WBA, WBC & WBO Middleweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Bernard Hopkins vs Oscar De La Hoya (IBF, Lineal, The Ring, WBA, WBC & WBO Middleweight Title)</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<summary>After losing the WBA and WBC light middleweight titles to Shane Mosley in September 2003, five-division world champion Oscar De La Hoya decided to move up to the middleweight division to challenge undisputed middleweight champion Bernard Hopkins, who had been middleweight champion for nearly a decade and had not lost a fight in over 11 years. Before the two would fight each other, De La Hoya and Hopkins would first have to get past Felix Sturm and Robert Allen, respectively. In a doubleheader event broadcast by HBO pay-per-view, Hopkins easily defeated Allen by a lopsided unanimous decision to retain his undisputed title, but De La Hoya struggled in his match with Sturm and only narrowly escaped with a unanimous decision (115–113 on all three scorecards) to capture Sturm's WBO middleweight title (becoming the first six-division champion in boxing history) and officially put his anticipated match with Hopkins on. De La Hoya and Hopkins would proceed with their fight and agreed to a catchweight – a rarity for championship fights – of 158 pounds, in order to level the playing fields for the smaller De La Hoya, who had only one middleweight bout to his credit. Because of Hopkins' size advantage and his vast experience in the middlweight division, De La Hoya, for the first time in his professional career, was considered the "underdog", with the odds makers in Las Vegas favoring Hopkins at 2–1. De La Hoya, however, was scheduled to make a career high $30 million, while Hopkins would net $10 million, also a career high.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/9fZpW8Fm09o?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/uX-QzQOiENw?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/76/0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://images.performgroup.com/di/library/sporting_news/f4/f3/bernard-hopkins-oscar-de-la-hoya-getty-ftr-121716_1o6mj8jfyidop1agd88kk5u8gk.jpg?t=231370177</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Ike Ibeabuchi vs David Tua (WBC Heavyweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Ike Ibeabuchi vs David Tua (WBC Heavyweight Title)</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<summary>The Ike Ibeabuchi versus David Tua fight, which took place on 7 June 1997 at the Arco Arena in Sacramento, California, has entered into heavyweight boxing folklore. Its fame owes nothing to the tangible laurels that the victor earned – the WBC International strap being an unusually meaningless bauble even by the absurd standards of boxing’s proliferation of governing bodies. Instead it owes its legendary status to its breathlessly relentless pace and beautiful brutality; a brutality reflected by a remarkable and oft-quoted statistic - of all the heavyweight fights analysed since 1985 by CompuBox, Ibeabuchi-Tua featured more punches thrown than any other heavyweight contest, a staggering 1,730 in twelve rounds, of which Ibeabuchi threw a barely believable 975 at a jaw dropping average of 81.25 per round. By way of comparison, the famed Thrilla in Manilla, the benchmark by which all heavyweight wars are usually measured, saw 1,591 punches thrown in fourteen rounds.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/PZ6w9I4I4T8?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/35yD86f4Nq4?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/QysfCHcgraI?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>https://static1.squarespace.com/static/55105517e4b0dda71296b0a6/t/593810d29de4bb646dd0c0bc/1496861879345/ibeabuchi-banner-02.jpg?format=2500w</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://static1.squarespace.com/static/55105517e4b0dda71296b0a6/t/59383b856b8f5b82cbd9b424/1496874118049/IKE_TUA011.jpg?format=2500w</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Anthony Joshua vs Dillian Whyte (British Heavyweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Anthony Joshua vs Dillian Whyte</title>
		<year>2015</year>
		<summary>Joshua, The Olympic champion (14-0-KO14) put his Commonwealth title on the line against Whyte (16-0-KO13), who beat him in 2009 when the pair were amateur fighters. Joshua headed for The O2 as a clear favourite to stop his rival Londoner but with Whyte appearing to ruffle his opponent's feathers slightly in the lead-up to their long-awaited rematch.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video-52974264_171340024</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video-92785906_171690931</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.matchroomsport.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/xx-Joshua-v-Whyte-1000x600.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://www.matchroomsport.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/xx-Joshua-v-Whyte-1000x600.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Anthony Joshua vs Wladimir Klitschko (IBF, IBO & WBA Heavyweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Anthony Joshua vs Wladimir Klitschko (IBF, IBO & WBA Heavyweight Titles)</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<summary>On Sat April 29, 2017 at the Wembley Stadium in London, England, former heavyweight champion Wladimir Klitschko (64-4, 53 KO) looked to get his belt back when he took on Anthony Joshua (18-0, 18 KO) for the IBF, vacant WBA (Super) and IBO heavyweight titles. It was Klitschko’s first appearance since losing a 12-round decision to awkward Englishman Tyson Fury in 2015. Klitschko was also competing in England for the first time since defeating Monte Barrett via seventh-round TKO back in 2000. As for Joshua, it would mark his first fight since destroying Eric Molina via third-round TKO the December before.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/lu90_aobkq4?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CX_6DjS0XfNYSDxhzArzIL</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/Ay8pLAn6dJA?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CX_6DjS0XfNYSDxhzArzIL</sublink>
		<sublink>https://openload.co/embed/OqBgdrgy_ck/</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://i.imgur.com/ZSioKnd.png</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://i.imgur.com/irkw2Gy.png</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Amir Khan vs Marcos Maidana (WBA Light Welterweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Amir Khan vs Marcos Maidana (WBA Light Welterweight Title)</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<summary>Light welterweight titlist Amir Khan and interim titlist Marcos Maidana reached an agreement to meet on December 11, 2010. The bout was for Khan's WBA Light Welterweight Title, which Khan successfully defended, winning via unanimous decision. The fight was awarded Fight of the Year by the Boxing Writers Association of America.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/SBtkFdewovk?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video-20701067_172223480</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.fightsaga.com/media/k2/items/cache/88d9a0cb55d81b8a3601ff79f8d5c68d_XL.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mjfQFaDfw5c/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Lennox Lewis vs Vitali Klitschko (IBO, The Ring & WBC Heavyweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Lennox Lewis vs Vitali Klitschko (IBO, The Ring & WBC Heavyweight Titles)</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<summary>Lennox Lewis vs Vitali Klitschko, billed as "Battle of the Titans", was a professional boxing match contested on June 21, 2003 for the WBC, IBO, The Ring and Lineal Heavyweight Championships.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/RMjyJQClP8o?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://vk.com/video20548138_171162883</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://africanring.co.za/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/LENNOX-LEWIS-VS-VITALI-KLITSCHKO.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RMjyJQClP8o/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Floyd Mayweather Jr. vs Canelo Álvarez (The Ring, WBA & WBC Light Middleweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Floyd Mayweather Jr. vs. Canelo Álvarez The Ring, WBA & WBC Light Middleweight Titles)</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<summary>Floyd Mayweather Jr. vs. Canelo Álvarez, billed as "The One", was a boxing light middleweight championship superfight. The bout was held on September 14, 2013, in the MGM Grand Garden Arena, at the MGM Grand Hotel & Casino in Las Vegas, Nevada, United States, on Showtime PPV. Mayweather received $41.5 million for this fight before taking into account pay-per-view sales.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>https://youtu.be/LflnwWXmyHc?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</link>
	<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/e/ee/MayweatherVsCanelo.jpg/230px-MayweatherVsCanelo.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Ay9Ege0Bzeg/hq720.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Floyd Mayweather Jr. vs Manny Pacquiao (The Ring, WBC & WBO Welterweight Titles)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Floyd Mayweather Jr. vs Manny Pacquiao (The Ring, WBC & WBO Welterweight Titles)</title>
		<year>2015</year>
		<summary>After years of rumors, speculation, arguments and failed negotiations, boxing’s biggest fight was finally to become a reality. The long-awaited showdown between Floyd Mayweather Jr. and Manny Pacquiao arrived at a time when the sweet science was experiencing something of a renaissance, with a number of interesting and entertaining cards populating network television thus far in 2015. This one, however, trumped them all. Naysayers argued that Mayweather-Pacquiao should have happened in 2009, but the fact remains that both men where still the best in the division. While neither was in his physical prime, Mayweather continued to turn back all challengers, and Pacquiao had rebounded strongly from a controversial loss to Timothy Bradley and a devastating knockout defeat against Juan Manuel Marquez to revive his brilliant career. Mayweather-Pacquiao was a major event, the kind of happening that makes casual sports fans clear their calendars to make sure they see it</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>http://thevideo.me/mn9do38etc8i</sublink>
		<sublink>https://thevideo.me/pqlu4e7wr7hg</sublink>
		<sublink>https://thevideo.me/v6szttnanyuu</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/d/d9/Mayweather_Pacquiao_Official_Poster.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3oVGVJHogvI/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Tommy "The Duke" Morrison Documentary[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Tommy "The Duke" Morrison Documentary</title>
		<year>1990</year>
		<summary>Tommy David Morrison (January 2, 1969 – September 1, 2013) was an American professional boxer who competed from 1988 to 1996, and held the WBO heavyweight title in 1993. He retired from boxing in 1996 when he tested positive for HIV, but returned for two more fights in 2007 and 2008. Morrison is best known for starring alongside Sylvester Stallone in the 1990 film Rocky V. Morrison previously attempted a comeback to boxing in 2006, claiming he had tested negative for HIV. In August 2013, Morrison's mother announced that her son was in the final stages of AIDS, and he died on September 1, 2013.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>https://youtu.be/8u61lHIoMx4?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.boxinginsider.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/09/morrison_1800797a.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DlEW1wpStAM/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Prince Naseem vs Kevin Kelley (WBO Featherweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Prince Naseem vs Kevin Kelley (WBO Featherweight Title)</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<summary>Highlights of the extremely exciting bout between two great southpaw fighters; Prince Naseem Hamed and “The Flushing Flash” Kevin Kelley in December 1997. Kelley came in with a record of 47-1-2 with only one loss in 1995 against Alenjandro Gonzalez while The Prince came in undefeated with a record of 28-0 with 26 knockouts. This was Kelley’s 51st career bout. Hamed was making the 9th defense of his WBO Featherweight title. Prior to this fight, Hamed had wins over Daniel Alicea, Billy Hardy, Tom Johnson, Manuel Medina, Steve Robinson and Juan Polo Perez while Kelley had victories over Gregorio Vargas, Derrick Gainer, Troy Dorsey, Orlando Fernandez, Jesus Salud, Jesse Benavides, Louie Espinoza. The fight was explosive from start to finish, as both fighters scored multiple knockdowns against on another throughout the short but highly competitive battle with amazing back and forth action where power punches are traded non stop.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/vV4Bn1nkJ_E?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/M_lJKInqhtU?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/VqrwAqkTKQE?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/360/0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2015/06/14/23/16-Hamed-V-Kelley-Getty.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Aaron Pryor vs Alexis Arguello I (WBA Light Welterweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Aaron Pryor vs Alexis Arguello I (WBA Light Welterweight Title)</title>
		<year>1982</year>
		<summary>Arguello had previously won three boxing titles (at Featherweight, Junior Lightweight and Lightweight) and hoped to become the first boxer ever to win world titles in four divisions by adding the Jr. Welterweight title. The broadcaster, HBO, had televised two of Arguello's previous fights. Pryor had no previous telecasts on that network, despite a record of 31 wins and no losses, with 29 knockouts. Both fighters had radically opposing public images. Arguello was suave, sophisticated, and extremely humble about his impressive accomplishments, which garnered him great admiration from both the boxing community and the media . Pryor, on the other hand, was fearsome, intimidating and, despite possessing great talent and having been a peer of greats Sugar Ray Leonard and Thomas Hearns, was the recipient of limited media coverage.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/O39psaFgk_U?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/782/0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/6d/4e/47/6d4e47fb0a5b72c883a98cead68d6edd.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Aaron Pryor vs Alexis Arguello II (WBA Light Welterweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Aaron Pryor vs Alexis Arguello II (WBA Light Welterweight Title)</title>
		<year>1983</year>
		<summary>When Arguello vs Pryor II was officially announced, anticipation was just as high as for the first bout, but for different reasons. The first time around what spurred ticket sales was adulation for Arguello and the expectation of history being made; this time it was the more straight-forward anticipation of straight-up excitement, of another action-packed war, as that first scintillating clash was widely regarded as one of the most exciting fights of recent years. Fewer pundits were now willing to bet the farm on Arguello seizing that fourth world title and thus the allure and magic of the initial Arguello vs Pryor battle was conspicuously absent. Instead of a massive football stadium filled to the rafters with delirious Latin Americans, the rematch was held at the more banal environs of Caesar’s Palace in Las Vegas.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>
		<sublink>https://youtu.be/3xxB3p8Qwwo?list=PLAH3EL0VqG7CHyEE3OSblbx6WJEb0x8kj</sublink>
	</link>
	<thumbnail>http://www.kofightposters.com/images/items/858/0.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/6d/4e/47/6d4e47fb0a5b72c883a98cead68d6edd.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<plugin>
	<title>[COLOR white]Salvador Sánchez[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Salvador Sánchez</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<summary>Salvador Sánchez Narváez (January 26, 1959 – August 12, 1982) was a Mexican boxer born in the town of Santiago Tianguistenco, Estado de México. Sanchez was the WBC and lineal featherweight champion from 1980 to 1982. Many of his contemporaries as well as boxing writers believe that, had it not been for his premature death, Sanchez could have gone on to become the greatest Featherweight boxer of all time. Sánchez died on August 12, 1982 in a car accident from Querétaro to San Luis Potosí. Sánchez started his professional career at the age of 16, as a teenager (after a brief amateur career consisting of reportedly 4 amateur bouts) he started piling up wins against tough Mexican opposition. His first fight of note came in his 19th professional fight against the Mexican bantamweight champion Antonio Becerra. Becerra proved too experienced for the young Sánchez, the bout ended in a split decision defeat for Sánchez. Sánchez started his professional career at the age of 16, as a teenager (after a brief amateur career consisting of reportedly 4 amateur bouts) he started piling up wins against tough Mexican opposition. His first fight of note came in his 19th professional fight against the Mexican bantamweight champion Antonio Becerra. Becerra proved too experienced for the young Sánchez, the bout ended in a split decision defeat for Sánchez. Sánchez kept on fighting and moved to the Featherweight division. Soon he had beaten people like the Puerto Rican featherweight champion Felix Trinidad Sr., on his way to securing a title shot at world champion Danny "Little Red" Lopez, a popular TV fighter of the late 1970s who was an impressive fighter and had won some spectacular fights against the likes of former world champion David Kotei (twice), Juan Malvares and Mike Ayala. Confident and hard to beat, Lopez was beaten by the 21-year-old Sánchez, who knocked out the defending champion in 13 rounds in Phoenix, Arizona, United States on February 2, 1980. Sanchez defended his title for the first time with a 15-round unanimous decision against Ruben Castillo (47–1). Thinking it was just a case of 'beginner's luck' (as it was Sánchez's first world title fight ever), Lopez looked for a rematch and this he got, in Las Vegas. This time Sánchez defeated Lopez by 14th-round TKO. In his next fight, he defeated Patrick Ford (15–0). On December 13, 1980, Sánchez defeated future champion Juan Laporte by unanimous decision. Sánchez then defended his title against Roberto Castanon (43–1–0) and scored a win over Nicky Perez (50–3–0). Then undefeated World Jr Featherweight champion Wilfredo Gómez (32–0–1) went up in weight and challenged Sánchez. Sánchez retained the crown by a knockout in round eight on August 21, 1981, in Las Vegas, and Gómez had to return to the Jr. Featherweight division. With that victory, Salvador was an unknown to the casual boxing fan no more. He became a household name all over the United States that night. In his next fight, he defeated Olympic medalist Pat Cowdell by split decision. His defense vs unheralded Jorge "Rocky" Garcia was the first fight featuring two featherweights ever to be televised by HBO. He beat Garcia punch after punch, but the challenger gave honor to his nickname, an unknown fighter who lasts the distance with the world champion. On July 21, 1982, Sánchez faced future champion Azumah Nelson at Madison Square Garden. Nelson, a late substitute for mandatory challenger Mario Miranda, was unknown at the time however, and was expected to only go a few rounds with the champ. It was an intense battle, with Sánchez managing to drop his young charge in the 7th round. After that they engaged in violent exchange after violent exchange. In the 15th, Sánchez broke out finally, connecting with a serious combination that dropped the challenger almost outside the ring. Referee Tony Perez had to stop the fight seconds later. Azumah Nelson went on to have a glittering career and was inducted into the International Boxing Hall of Fame in 2004. Sanchez's dominance as featherweight champion was such that he held title defense victories over the next three fighters (LaPorte, Gomez, and Nelson) who won the WBC title after his death. Also notably, he went 4-0, all four wins by knockouts, against fellow members of the International Boxing Hall of Fame (Danny Lopez twice-KO 13, KO 14-Wilfredo Gomez-KO 8-and Azumah Nelson-KO 15)</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PLS8IdtYX-ARu7oB_JAGISyIfAeyM9lGwr/</link>
	<thumbnail>http://assets.nydailynews.com/polopoly_fs/1.2433840.1447436450!/img/httpImage/image.jpg_gen/derivatives/article_750/eastwest2-3-web.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/q1SuGMosX84/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</plugin>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Bermane Stiverne vs Deontay Wilder (WBC Heavyweight Title)[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Bermane Stiverne vs Deontay Wilder (WBC Heavyweight Title)</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<summary>Saturday 17th January 2017, in Las Vegas, Bermane Stiverne was to defend his WBC heavyweight title against undefeated knockout machine Deontay Wilder. It had been 32 up and 32 down for Wilder in his career so far, and nobody had escaped the fourth round against him. But Wilder had never faced an opponent as dangerous as Stiverne. He was an experienced boxer with explosive power of his own. There had not been a heavyweight bout this big in the United States in years. Two big men with dangerous punching power would get together in the world's fight capital.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>https://vid.me/tzM0</link>
	<thumbnail>http://roundbyroundboxing.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Stiverne-Wilder-Tale-of-the-Tape.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://i.dailymail.co.uk/i/pix/2015/01/18/24CDE02700000578-0-image-a-16_1421559310160.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Mike Tyson[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Mike Tyson</title>
		<year>2017</year>
		<summary>One of the most frightening human beings ever to step into the boxing ring, Mike Tyson was the model of the supreme gladiator - unbeaten and unbeatable. Never before had one individual captured the attention of the wider world via sport except Muhammad Ali. Tyson blazed through the heavyweight division after turning professional in 1985, winning the WBC title in 1986, before adding the IBF and WBA belts the following year to unify the division. In 1988 – arguably his peak – he flattened former leader Larry Holmes, Tony Tubbs, and Michael Spinks.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>plugin://plugin.video.youtube/playlist/PL13cOaNQW6HM8GZpedkwTRnTC3Hdg2RBP/</link>
	<thumbnail>http://movies.dosthana.com/sites/default/files/image-gallery/Mike%20Tyson-Pic.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/INv2pi5UUBs/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</item>

<item>
	<title>[COLOR white]Dillian Whyte vs Dereck Chisora[/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title>Dillian Whyte vs Dereck Chisora</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<summary>Chisora was desperate to claw back some respect after his bizarre attitude in the build up while Whyte was be eager to shut up his opponent once and for all with a quick knockout. Whyte certainly had the speed on Chisora, but the 32-year-old had been up against better opposition in his career than the 28-year-old. Many believed Whyte was on the up in the heavyweight division and he was looking to crack Chisora’s steel chin from the word go. Chisora’s relentless nature in the ring was believed to work against him in the end or help to blitz Whyte. This one was probably one of the hardest to call, but with so much anger swelling around Chisora at that moment in time, Whyte could be spooked. That’s what Chisora was hoping for anyway.</summary>
	</meta>
	<link>http://streamcloud.eu/zmfjxs55tjtg/Boxing.2016.12.10.Dillian.Whyte.Vs.Dereck.Chisora.mp4.html</link>
	<thumbnail>http://atbf1.allthebestfights.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/whyte-vs-chisora-poster-2016-12-10.jpg</thumbnail>
	<fanart>http://e1.365dm.com/16/11/16-9/20/skysports-dillian-whyte-dereck-chisora_3821902.jpg?20161101124302</fanart>
</item>

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

< item>
	<title>[COLOR white][/COLOR]</title>
	<meta>
		<content>movie</content>
		<imdb></imdb>
		<title></title>
		<year></year>
		<summary></summary>
	</meta>
	<link></link>
	<thumbnail></thumbnail>
	<fanart></fanart>
</ item>